<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fukuoka</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="placer">Hi</string>
    <string name="why_here_header">Why Here?</string>
    <string name="history_header">History</string>
    <string name="culture_header">Culture</string>
    <string name="restaurant_header">Restaurants</string>

    <string name="why_here_0_title">Startup Economy</string>
    <string name="why_here_0_information">Fukuoka\’s startup ecosystem is still in its early days.
                Not as many startups here as in other big cities like Tokyo.  It has its cons (obviously), everything has to be built, we don’t have a lot of investors here,
                not so many English meetups etc. But it also has many advantages. The community being young and still small
                it is easier to get recognition and get your name on the map. People are also much more motivated.
                We all have to work together to grow the ecosystem and people are willing to help and share their experience.</string>

    <string name="why_here_1_title">Demographics</string>
    <string name="why_here_1_information">Fukuoka is a medium size city (1.5million habitants) and its population is pretty young.
                Average of 40 years old-ish. This makes of the city a very active city, very lively.
                Business wise, a young population means that people are more open minded,
                more prone to change and willing to accept new concepts.</string>

    <string name="history_0_title">Fukuoka Castle</string>
    <string name="history_0_information">The ruins of Fukuoka Castle (福岡城跡, Fukuokajōato)
                are located in the middle of the city in Maizuru Park, named after the castle\'s alias, Maizuru
                Castle. During the Edo Period (1603-1867), Fukuoka Castle used to be the largest castle on Kyushu,
                but it was almost completely torn down after the Meiji Restoration as an unwanted symbol of the feudal
                past.</string>

    <string name="history_1_title">Kushida Shrine</string>
    <string name="history_1_information">A Shinto shrine located in Hakata-ku, Fukuoka, Japan. Dedicated to
                Amaterasu and Susanoo, it is said to have been founded in 757. The Hakata Gion Yamakasa festival is centred
                on the shrine.</string>

    <string name="culture_0_title">Culture</string>
    <string name="culture_0_information">Fukuoka is bordered by the ocean to the north, east, and west, and
                each of its coastlines has a unique character. Breathtaking views and outdoor activities can be
                enjoyed in the area\'s mild climate.
                The prefectural capital of Fukuoka City overlooks the Port of Hakata, a harbor that has long facilitated
                the region\'s prosperity through trade with other parts of Asia. In addition to being the administrative and
                economic heart of the prefecture, Fukuoka is a lively commercial center from which trends in culture and fashion
                filter out to other parts of Japan. International flights from a variety of countries fly into and out of
                this "gateway to Asia" and the city\'s shops make it easy for tourists to satisfy their urge to splurge.
                Fukuoka also boasts popular annual festivals with long histories. The Hakata Dontaku Festival, which takes place
                on May 3-4, dates back to the twelfth century. Originally a means of celebrating the New Year, it is now a major
                event in which about 20,000 residents parade through the city dressed in a variety of costumes, attracting as many
                as two million spectators.</string>

    <string name="restaurant_0_title">Hakata Miyachiku</string>
    <string name="restaurant_0_information">Imagining to be a healing space in mother nature of Miyazaki and country of fairy tale,
                Fully enjoy the delicious taste from Miyazaki Beef.
                Private dining room available. Restaurants as delivering the philosophy of producers
                For being the bridge between clients and producers, Miyazaki Japan cows, growing from the good shiny environment of Kawasaki,
                are continuously processed through the producing line of our company and distributed into our affiliated restaurants.
                Fukuoka Hakata, the birthplace of Kyushu, offers the safe and worry-free Miyazaki Japan beef,
                and all kind of other tasty food of Miyazaki.</string>

    <string name="restaurant_1_title">Kawataro</string>
    <string name="restaurant_1_information">With over 40 years of history, we were the first restaurant in Japan to have
                an on-site fish tank. Enjoy unbeatably fresh seafood and authentic Japanese dishes and some new flavors too.</string>
</resources>
